There are many techniques for settling your baby.
هناك العديد من الأساليب لتهدئة طفلك.
Listening to other parents advice can be helpful
يمكن أن يكون الاستماع إلى نصائح الآباء الآخرين مفيدًا
but remember that every baby is different and what works for someone else may not
لكن تذكري أن كل طفل يختلف عن الآخر
William's six weeks old
يبلغ "ويليام" ستة أسابيع من العمر
when we first came out of hospital we had no idea what we're doing
عندما خرجنا من المستشفى لأول مرة لم تكن لدينا أي فكرة عما نفعله
and what would work with him and what would not work with him
وماذا يناسبه معه وما لا يناسبه
i mean i guess.
انا أعتقد..
We still don't really know what we're doing is right.
ما زلنا لا نعرف حقًا أن ما نقوم به هو الصواب.
or what we're doing is wrong
أو أن ما نفعله خطأ
We're at least now learning what works with him
نحن نتعلم الآن على الأقل ما الذي يناسبه وما لا يناسبه.
So..
لذا..
to try settle him.
لمحاولة تهدئته.
talking and..
التحدث معه, و ..
going shh..
قول: صه ..
shh..
صه ..
Perfect.
ممتاز.
Cornelius is only really started to respond to our settling techniques in the past
بدأ "كورنيليوس" بالفعل في الاستجابة لأساليب تهدئتنا
week being six weeks old
في الأسبوع الماضي بعمر ستة أسابيع
he has a lot of whims he loves being put
لديه طُرق كثيرة يفضلها
and then patting his head and then just rubbing his tummy as well
ثم اربت على رأسه ثم افرك بطنه أيضًا
really seem to settle him down and.
يبدو حقًا أنه يهدأ بفعل هذا.
We find as soon as he stops crying
و نجد انه حالما يتوقف عن البكاء
to stop doing anything and just leave him to
نتوقف عن فعل أي شيء وتركه ليهدأ بمفرده
there's no one thing , just keep trying different things
ليس هناك طريقة واحدة ، فقط استمر في تجربة أشياء مختلفة
and you think you've got him worked out one minute.
وتعتقد أنك علمت الآن ما يُفضله .
And then it doesn't work and you gonna to try something new
وبعد ذلك لا تنجح وستجرب شيئًا جديدًا
we were walking around in circles
كنا حائرين
so it was kind of a bit of a rhythm to it.
كان هنالك طريقة مُعينة
we've got a little water feature..
لدينا ميزة مائية صغيرة ..
out in our backyard..
في الفناء الخلفي لدينا ..
a little fountain
نافورة صغيرة
And the noise of that seems to work quite well ..
ويبدو أن ضوضاء ذلك تعمل بشكل جيد ..
but then again it won't work every time.
ولكن ايضاً لن تعمل في كل مرة.
And we've got a cd that she really likes.
ولدينا قرص مضغوط تحبه حقًا.
So ,we'd Play that
لذلك ، سوف نستمع لذلك
and that could work.
ويمكن أن ينجح ذلك.
rocking, patting,..
هزها، التربيت عليها، ..
A lot of singing and making up songs with her name
الكثير من الغناء وتأليف الأغاني باسمها
and sometimes it's bath ,maybe a bath would work.
وأحيانًا يكون حمامًا ، ربما يكون الحمام مناسبًا.
taking her outside into a park
اصطحابها للخارج إلى حديقة
Also realizing that sometimes when she hasn't settled after a period of time
كما ادركنا أنه في بعض الأحيان عندما لا تهدء بعد فترة من الزمن
to possibly..
ربما ..
Leave it alone for awhile.
نتركها لوحدها لبعض الوقت.
and get the stress levels down.
وخفض مستويات التوتر.
She keeps on building up, and she kinda get louder and louder and.
إنها تستمر في البُكاء ، وهي ترفع صوتها تدريجياً.
so the things you're doing aren't working.
لذا فإن الأشياء التي تقوم بها لا تعمل.
I think it's just not to panic
أعتقد أنه لا يجب ان نذعر
something eventually will work.
شيء ما سينجخ معها في النهاية.
she eventually will stop crying.
ستتوقف عن البكاء في النهاية.
Nice sweetheart.
حبيبتي الجميلة.